export const questions = [
    {
        question: "What is the first Pokémon in the Pokédex?",
        answer: "Bulbasaur",
        tag: "Pokémon",
        isBookmarked: false,
        answerShown: false,
    },
    {
        question: "Which Pokémon is known as the 'Electric Mouse'?",
        answer: "Pikachu",
        tag: "Pokémon",
        isBookmarked: false,
        answerShown: false,
    },
    {
        question: "What type is Charizard?",
        answer: "Fire/Flying",
        tag: "Pokémon",
        isBookmarked: false,
        answerShown: false,
    },
    {
        question: "Which Pokémon evolves into Gyarados?",
        answer: "Magikarp",
        tag: "Pokémon",
        isBookmarked: false,
        answerShown: false,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the signature move of Mewtwo?",
        answer: "Psystrike",
        tag: "Pokémon",
        isBookmarked: false,
        answerShown: false,
    },
    {
        question: "Which Pokémon is known as the 'Legendary Pokémon' of time?",
        answer: "Dialga",
        tag: "Pokémon",
        isBookmarked: false,
        answerShown: false,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the evolution of Eevee that is a Water type?",
        answer: "Vaporeon",
        tag: "Pokémon",
        isBookmarked: false,
        answerShown: false,
    },
    {
        question: "Which Pokémon is known for its ability to change forms?",
        answer: "Deoxys",
        tag: "Pokémon",
        isBookmarked: false,
        answerShown: false,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Ash's first Pokémon?",
        answer: "Pikachu",
        tag: "Pokémon",
        isBookmarked: false,
        answerShown: false,
    },
    {
        question: "Which Pokémon is known as the 'Guardian of the Sea'?",
        answer: "Lugia",
        tag: "Pokémon",
        isBookmarked: false,
        answerShown: false,
    }
];